https://www.russandrews.com/us/privacy-and-cookies/

Basket
(0 Items, $0.00)
+44 1539 797300
Search
Select CountryEUROWUnited Kingdom
0 Items, $0.00
PowerRuss Andrews Power CablesRuss Andrews Power DistributionPower ConditionersVoltage ClampsPlugs and socketsCleaning and maintenanceFusesPower SuppliesBalanced Mains UnitsCablesMini InterconnectsDIN InterconnectsTone Arm cablesNetwork CablesHeadphone cablesJumper CablesInterconnect AccessoriesSpeaker Cable accessoriesSystem racks & supportsTorlyte equipment platformsTorlyte Equipment RacksTorlyte Turntable SupportTorlyte Audio Visual RacksTorlyte speaker standsEquipment spikes & spiked feetEquipment feetSupport accessoriesOther Good StuffCleaning & enhancingBooksOptical Disc AccessoriesResonance controlTurntable mats, belts & accessoriesLens cleanersAdaptorsSystem set-up discsGift VouchersDisc anti-static productsNoise reduction accessoriesToolsSolderAerialsLinn LP12 partsIsoMike CDsServicesHardwareEverything elseEquipment UpgradesDIY UpgradesNew ProductsNew ProductsManufacturerADD-PowrAKGAudio Desk SystemeCaigDigital Video EssentialsEtymotic ResearchIsoMikeKimber KableLightDimsLinn ProductsMA RecordingsMeridian AudioMobile FidelityOrigin LiveREGARingmatRoonRupert Neve DesignsRuss AndrewsSpears & MunsilStack AudioStasis CleanersSvalander AudioWattGateWBTOtherOffersPre-ownedWarehouse Clearance
60 Day Money Back Guarantee
Lifetime Warranty
Upgrade Program
Superb Service
Home > Privacy Information
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. As always our policy is not to disclose customer information to any third parties (except as explained in sections 1 and 3 below), so you won't get 'junk mail' as a result of being on our mailing list.
If you want to know about how we use the information we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy, then read on.
1. The information we collect and how we use it
When you register/place an order we need to know your name, postal address, delivery address (if different), e-mail address and telephone number. When placing an order you will be asked to provide credit or debit card information. These payment details will be protected by encryption and for optimal security are only retained temporarily.
We gather this information to allow us to process your registration and process any orders you may place. The relevant information is then used by us to communicate with you on any matters relating to your order and the provision of goods and services in general.
We would like to provide you with information about special offers, product and service promotions we think may be of interest to you and special features of our website. If you would rather not receive this information, please indicate this preference in 'My Account' on this website (if you have registered). Alternatively, to remove yourself from our e-mail list send an email with your name to info@russandrewsusa.com, and to remove yourself from our postal list send an e-mail with your name and address (or customer number) to info@russandrewsusa.com.
We do not provide your information to any third parties except:
To monitor website usage we may use aggregate information and statistics in order to help us develop the website and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual.
To monitor and improve the goods or services we provide, from time to time we may provide your information to our customer services agencies for research and analysis purposes. We or our agents and sub-contractors may contact you by post, e-mail or telephone to ask you for your feedback and comments on our goods or services. We completely understand that you may not wish to give us feedback.
2. How we protect your information
The internet is not a secure medium. However we have put in place security procedures to encrypt sensitive information using SSL security.
We also keep your information confidential. The internal procedures of Russ Andrews USA Inc cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information.
3. Sale of business
If this business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.
4. Updating your details
If any of the information that you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, name or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by one of the following methods:
Amend your details in 'My Account' on this website
Phone us on 801-334-5510
E-mail us at info@russandrewsusa.com
5. Your consent
By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. We will also e-mail you should we make any changes so that you may consent to our use of your information in that way. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes.
6. How to contact us
We welcome your views about our website and our privacy policy. Contact Us if you have any questions or would like to make any comments.
Privacy Policy
Back to Top
Recently Viewed
Recently Viewed
You can view your recently viewed items here.
2B Moreland Court, Westmorland Business ParkKendal, Cumbria LA9 6NS, UK Registered in England No. 1968621VAT Registered No. 442 798 517
© 2017 Russ Andrews Accessories Ltd
ecommerce by Paraspar
About Us
Find out more about us.
Read more
About Us
About Us
About Kimber Kable
Why do we sell Kimber Kable?
2B Moreland Court, Westmorland Business ParkKendal, Cumbria LA9 6NS, UK Registered in England No. 1968621VAT Registered No. 442 798 517
Why should I upgrade my power?
Upgrading your power in 10 steps
Cabling
How much to spend - Russ's 10% rule
How to upgrade your signal cables
What is attenuation?
Don't miss out! Subscribe to our regular emails and you'll be the first to hear about new products and offers.
The email address is not valid, please try again
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
We use cookies to give you a better service. Continue browsing if you're happy with this, or find out more about cookies.
Accept & Close
X
